// src/data/questions.js
const questions = [
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Andhra Pradesh?",
      options: ["N. Chandrababu Naidu", "Y. S. Jagan Mohan Reddy", "Kiran Kumar Reddy", "Y. S. Rajasekhara Reddy"],
      answer: "Y. S. Jagan Mohan Reddy",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Arunachal Pradesh?",
      options: ["Pema Khandu", "Nabam Tuki", "Kalikho Pul", "Dorjee Khandu"],
      answer: "Pema Khandu",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Assam?",
      options: ["Sarbananda Sonowal", "Himanta Biswa Sarma", "Tarun Gogoi", "Prafulla Kumar Mahanta"],
      answer: "Himanta Biswa Sarma",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Bihar?",
      options: ["Lalu Prasad Yadav", "Sushil Kumar Modi", "Nitish Kumar", "Tejashwi Yadav"],
      answer: "Nitish Kumar",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Chhattisgarh?",
      options: ["Raman Singh", "Bhupesh Baghel", "Ajit Jogi", "Mahendra Karma"],
      answer: "Bhupesh Baghel",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Goa?",
      options: ["Manohar Parrikar", "Pramod Sawant", "Laxmikant Parsekar", "Digambar Kamat"],
      answer: "Pramod Sawant",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Gujarat?",
      options: ["Anandiben Patel", "Bhupendra Patel", "Vijay Rupani", "Narendra Modi"],
      answer: "Bhupendra Patel",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Haryana?",
      options: ["Bhupinder Singh Hooda", "Manohar Lal Khattar", "Om Prakash Chautala", "Kiran Choudhry"],
      answer: "Manohar Lal Khattar",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Himachal Pradesh?",
      options: ["Jairam Thakur", "Virbhadra Singh", "Shanta Kumar", "Sukhvinder Singh Sukhu"],
      answer: "Sukhvinder Singh Sukhu",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Jharkhand?",
      options: ["Arjun Munda", "Raghubar Das", "Hemant Soren", "Babulal Marandi"],
      answer: "Hemant Soren",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Karnataka?",
      options: ["Siddaramaiah", "H. D. Kumaraswamy", "Basavaraj Bommai", "B. S. Yediyurappa"],
      answer: "Siddaramaiah",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Kerala?",
      options: ["Oommen Chandy", "Pinarayi Vijayan", "V. S. Achuthanandan", "A. K. Antony"],
      answer: "Pinarayi Vijayan",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Madhya Pradesh?",
      options: ["Shivraj Singh Chouhan", "Kamal Nath", "Digvijaya Singh", "Uma Bharti"],
      answer: "Shivraj Singh Chouhan",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Maharashtra?",
      options: ["Uddhav Thackeray", "Eknath Shinde", "Devendra Fadnavis", "Narayan Rane"],
      answer: "Eknath Shinde",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Manipur?",
      options: ["Okram Ibobi Singh", "N. Biren Singh", "Rishang Keishing", "Radha Binod Koijam"],
      answer: "N. Biren Singh",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Meghalaya?",
      options: ["Mukul Sangma", "Conrad Sangma", "Donkupar Roy", "James Sangma"],
      answer: "Conrad Sangma",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Mizoram?",
      options: ["Zoramthanga", "Lal Thanhawla", "Pu Laldenga", "C. L. Ruala"],
      answer: "Zoramthanga",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Nagaland?",
      options: ["Neiphiu Rio", "Sh√ºrhozelie Liezietsu", "T. R. Zeliang", "S. C. Jamir"],
      answer: "Neiphiu Rio",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Odisha?",
      options: ["Naveen Patnaik", "Mohan Charan Majhi", "Biju Patnaik", "Giridhar Gamang"],
      answer: "Mohan Charan Majhi",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Punjab?",
      options: ["Bhagwant Mann", "Amarinder Singh", "Charanjit Singh Channi", "Parkash Singh Badal"],
      answer: "Bhagwant Mann",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Rajasthan?",
      options: ["Vasundhara Raje", "Ashok Gehlot", "Sachin Pilot", "Bhairon Singh Shekhawat"],
      answer: "Ashok Gehlot",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Sikkim?",
      options: ["Pawan Kumar Chamling", "Prem Singh Tamang", "Nar Bahadur Bhandari", "B. B. Gurung"],
      answer: "Prem Singh Tamang",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Tamil Nadu?",
      options: ["Edappadi K. Palaniswami", "M. K. Stalin", "J. Jayalalithaa", "O. Panneerselvam"],
      answer: "M. K. Stalin",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Telangana?",
      options: ["K. Chandrashekar Rao", "K. T. Rama Rao", "Etela Rajender", "T. Harish Rao"],
      answer: "K. Chandrashekar Rao",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Tripura?",
      options: ["Manik Sarkar", "Biplab Kumar Deb", "Dr. Manik Saha", "Pradyot Bikram Manikya"],
      answer: "Dr. Manik Saha",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Uttar Pradesh?",
      options: ["Mulayam Singh Yadav", "Yogi Adityanath", "Akhilesh Yadav", "Mayawati"],
      answer: "Yogi Adityanath",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of Uttarakhand?",
      options: ["Trivendra Singh Rawat", "Pushkar Singh Dhami", "Harish Rawat", "Ramesh Pokhriyal"],
      answer: "Pushkar Singh Dhami",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Chief Minister of West Bengal?",
      options: ["Mamata Banerjee", "Siddhartha Shankar Ray", "Jyoti Basu", "Buddhadeb Bhattacharjee"],
      answer: "Mamata Banerjee",
    },
  ];
  
  export default questions;
  